{
    "1":{
        "prompt": "2+2?",
        "answer": "4",
        "understood": 1,
        "time":2
    },
    "2":{
        "prompt": "2x2",
        "answer": "4",
        "understood": 1,
        "time":2
    },
    "3":{
        "prompt": "2-2",
        "answer": "0",
        "understood": 1,
        "time":2
    },
    "4":{
        "prompt": "12-2",
        "answer": "10",
        "understood": 1,
        "time":2
    },
    "5":{
        "prompt": "12x2",
        "answer": "24",
        "understood": 1,
        "time":2
    },
    "6":{
        "prompt": "10-2",
        "answer": "8",
        "understood": 1,
        "time":2
    },
    "7":{
        "prompt": "10x2",
        "answer": "20",
        "understood": 1,
        "time":2
    },
    "8":{
        "prompt": "12-4",
        "answer": "8",
        "understood": 1,
        "time":2
    },
    "9":{
        "prompt": "12-6",
        "answer": "6",
        "understood": 1,
        "time":2
    },
    "10":{
        "prompt": "6x2",
        "answer": "12",
        "understood": 1,
        "time":2
    }
}